30 yo, 21/12/1983 in Rouen France (76)

DIGITAL ACCOUNT MANAGER / SOCIAL MEDIA CONSULTANT

With five years' experience in e-marketing services, I have developed strong abilities to network and develop key relationships. Passionate and proactive, I collect, interpret and learn from digital research; including features and tools active within the online advertising market. I'm a team player and I'm happy to share my knowledge with my colleagues. Reliable and with strength of conviction, I appreciate constructive criticism.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

| EXPERIENCE

E-MARKETING

SOCIAL MEDIA

ACCOUNT, PROJECT

& TEAM MANAGEMENT

DIGITAL ACCOUNT DIRECTOR | ISOBAR (Aegis Media - Paris)

January 2012 - January 2013

Develop, deliver and manage Digital full-services operations
> Digital creatives (websites, banners), Mobile (Banners, Apps) and Social Media

- Analyze briefs and lead teams to develop client specific strategies and associated tactics to drive client value
- Plan and delegate jobs and projects to community managers and creative teams
- Lead a team to manage timings, delivering all duties to agreed deadlines and budget
- o Briefing both the studio and development teams and management
- Working with clients to set KPIs for campaigns and ensuring performance is monitored closely against clients goals and contractual requirements
- o Client presentations and day-to-day client relationship management
- o Financial monitoring and forecasting
- o Participate in new business pitches
- o Support Head of Paid social advertising with campaign consultancy

// ACHIEVEMENTS

Diageo (MHD) 2012 -2013

Launch of the 'Baileys' and 'Grand Marnier' FR Fanpages

Objectives >> B: 100K fans the 1st year - 0,20% feedback GM: 50K fans the 1st year - 0,15% feedback Target reached >> B: 130K fans the 1st year - 0,25% feedback GM: 75K fans - 0,17% feedback

Other clients: J&J, PERFETTI, CARLSBERG Group, BEL Group, SFR...

SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNT MANAGER | NOYZ (Aegis Media - Paris)

June 2010 - Dec. 2011

Develop, deliver and manage Social Media strategies for Aegis Media clients
> Community Management, Paid social advertising, Blogs PR, Forums activation,
Buzz monitoring

SKILLS

- ✓ Deliver projects in a high level of quality within timeline and budget
- ✓ Resource planning
- ✓ Liaise and work closely with internal departments and external companies to the benefit of existing clients
- ✓ Able to multitask and manage within a fast changing environment
- ✓ Strategic thinker, analytical approach
- ✓ Ability to balance the need for strategic thinking with the need to deliver and get results
- ✓ Strong problem solving / troubleshooting skills
- ✓ Ability to work under a high level of pressure and with junior teams
- ✓ Strong negotiation skills

- o Implement social media strategies for major B2C brands accounts
- o Keep an eye on trends and determine potential applications for clients
- o Client presentations and day-to-day client relationship management
- Monitor delivery and budget against KPIs
- Manage reporting of performance to ensure team accountability and quality of delivery
- o Creation and implementation of new partnerships with Advertising Sales Houses and publishers to target new communities through forums
- Activating and monitoring paid social advertising
- o Work with developers on the socialization of website building projects
- o Team leader of 4 Community Managers
- o Financial monitoring and forecasting

// ACHIEVEMENTS

Philips 2010-2012

Launch of the different social hubs on Facebook FR, such as "Philips AVENT France", "Philips Self-Expression", and "Philips fait maison". This strategy had been put in place to be in line with the new brand positioning "Improving life through innovation". The goal was to promote an oriented customer vision through needs and not products or targets

Objectives >> 100K fans the 1st year - 0,15% feedback
Target reached >> + 150K fans - 0,18% feedback

Kellogg's 2010-2012

Launch and management of the 'Kellogg's Trésor' (Krave) and 'Squares' FR Fanpages

Objectives >> 100K fans the 1st year - 0,20% feedback
Target reached >> + 150K fans - 0,25% feedback

Other clients: **REEBOK, J&J, BKSA-CARLSBERG, BEIERSDORF, VIVARTE** (Caroll, Halles aux vêtements)...

DIGITAL PROJECT EXECUTIVE | OMNICOMMEDIAGROUP - Paris March 2008 – June 2010

E-Marketing consulting and project management; strategic planning and implementation for branded and direct responses campaigns > Display, PPC, affiliate programs, E-mailing, SEM, SEO and Mobile campaigns

- o Define scope, recommend approach and media planning bias
- Briefing and coordination of experts from all digital areas of expertise;
 Display (CPT, CPC, CPA, CPL), Affiliation, E-mailing, SEM, SEO and Mobile
- o Manage tactical execution of digital media strategy
- Analyze campaign performance against client KPIs and reports on any trends and insights to key stakeholders
- Campaigns optimization and reports
- o Client presentations and day-to-day client relationship management
- Financial monitoring

// ACHIEVEMENTS

Nissan 2008-2010

Launch and improvement of the affiliate program to generate leads (Tests Drive, e-leaflets)

Budget: 300/400K€ per year Objectives >> TD: 20€ - E-leaflet: 12€ Target reached >> TD: 15€ - E-leaflet: 8€

Hasbro 2010

Launch of Nerf range through a series of 4 online episodes (+teaser), produced by Kourtrajme.

Dealt with Dailymotion to promote videos (Pack Buzz) and negotiated to publish the teaser as "video star" on their Home Page initially (1st time)

Objectives >> 100K views per video Target reached >> average 150K views per video

Other clients: BARILLA, SONY PICTURES / SPHE ...

MARKETING PROJECT MANAGER | INSYWEB (IT company)

October 2005 - October 2007 (Part time student)

SALES PERSON | IMPACT SALES & MARKETING

December 2004 - June 2005

SALES PERSON | INDICIBLE

October 2002 - October 2004 (Part time student)

EDUCATION

Master Degree

Marketing / Communication and commercial strategies, specialty E-Commerce INSEEC, Paris 2008

Bachelor Degree

Business management, specialty Marketing / Communication Cefire-Esarc – INSEEC, Paris 2006

HND Level equivalent

Specialty Marketing / Communication IUT, Rouen 2004

| LANGUAGES

FRENCH: Mother tongue - ENGLISH: Advanced intermediate - GERMAN: Basic

| ITs SKILLS

Pack office / Photoshop CS / Illustrator CS NNR tools / ComScore / Kantar media / SIMM Tools of Buzz monitoring (Brandwatch, TrendyBuzz, Buzzmetrics, Viavoo...) HTML Knowledge